totalf1.com 2011-12-31

# F1, Formula 1: TotalF1.com - Privacy Policy

Total F1, and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

During the process of delivering our content to you, Total F1 does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address without your knowledge.

Your email address is required to join Total F1's mailing list, 'PPP Competition', the Forums and the News Grab Service, but this information is not shared or sold to any other party.

Total F1 does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information about its visitors such as time of visit, browser type, the type of operating system, screen resolution and screen colours, etc but this information is not linked to individual visitors. This information is used to assist Total F1 in producing web pages more suited to its average visitor.

Total F1's [F1 Inbox](http://mail.f1inbox.com/) service is run in conjunction with a third party (Everyone.net) who may collect personal information about you on signing up. When supplying personal information to Everyone.net, you can indicate your preference if you would like to be contacted to receive information and updates about Everyone.net's or Partner's services, or special offers from other companies through the Everyone.Benefits!™ program.

Everyone.net services may also utilise personally identifiable end-user information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to end-users based on their demographic and behavioural information. You can read Everyone.net's privacy policy [here](http://www.everyone.net/main/html/p_policy.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
